<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2015 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
-->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material World</string>
    <string name="city_ipsum">A city is a large and permanent human settlement.Although there is no
        agreement on how a city is distinguished from a town in general English language meanings,
        many cities have a particular administrative, legal, or historical status based on local law.
    </string>
    <string name="checkin">Checkin</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="raised">Raised</string>
    <string name="flat">Flat</string>
    <string name="chicago_text">Chicago is the third-most populous city in the United States. With over 2.7 million residents, it is the most populous city in the state of Illinois and the Midwestern United States, and the county seat of Cook County. The Chicago metropolitan area, often referred to as Chicagoland, has nearly 10 million people and is the third-largest in the U.S.</string>
    <string name="lasvegas_text">Las Vegas, Spanish for "The Meadows"), officially the City of Las Vegas and often known as simply Vegas, is a city in the United States, the most populous city in the state of Nevada, the county seat of Clark County, and the city proper of the Las Vegas Valley. Las Vegas is an internationally renowned major resort city known primarily for gambling, shopping, fine dining, and nightlife and is the leading financial, commercial, and cultural center for Southern Nevada.</string>
    <string name="neworleans_text">New Orleans is a major United States port and the largest city and metropolitan area in the state of Louisiana.</string>
    <string name="newyork_text">The City of New York, often called New York City or simply New York, is the most populous city in the United States.[9] Located at the southern tip of the state of New York, the city is the center of the New York metropolitan area, one of the most populous urban agglomerations in the world.</string>
    <string name="philadelphia_text">Philadelphia is the largest city in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania and the fifth-most populous in the United States, with an estimated population in 2014 of 1,560,297. In the Northeastern United States, at the confluence of the Delaware and Schuylkill rivers, Philadelphia is the economic and cultural anchor of the Delaware Valley, a metropolitan area home to 7.2 million people and the eighth-largest combined statistical area in the United States.</string>
    <string name="sanfrancisco_text">San Francisco, officially the City and County of San Francisco, is the cultural, commercial, and financial center of Northern California and the only consolidated city-county in California. San Francisco encompasses a land area of about 46.9 square miles on the northern end of the San Francisco Peninsula, which makes it the smallest county in the state. </string>

</resources>
